A Guide to the Commonwealth Fund records, Commission on A High Performance Health System, SG 3, Series 1 FA1458
Rockefeller Archive Center
Commonwealth Fund records, Commission on A High Performance Health System, SG 3, Series 1
2005-2009
Rockefeller Archive Center
Commonwealth Fund
FA1458
1.52 Cubic Feet 4 letter-size document boxes.
Arrangement
Records remain in original order, as received.
Conditions Governing Access
Open for research. Brittle or damaged items are available at the discretion of RAC.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
The Commonwealth Fund records were donated to RAC in 1985. The initial transfer of archival records to RAC began in 1986, and transfers continue on a regular basis. These Commission files were transferred to RAC as Accession 2007:077.
Scope and Contents
This series contains meeting books of the Commonwealth Fund Commission for a High Performance Health System, including but not limited to: agendas, background information, commission members, participants, attendees, and schedule of speakers and events.
- Commission on a High Performance Health System - Meetings, 2005 July (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Commission on a High Performance Health System - Meetings, 2005 November (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Commission on a High Performance Health System - Meetings, 2006 March (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Commission on a High Performance Health System - Meetings, 2006 July (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Commission on a High Performance Health System - Meetings, 2006 November (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Commission on a High Performance Health System - Meetings, 2006 November (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Commission on a High Performance Health System - Meetings, 2007 March (Box 2, Folder 7-8)
- Commission on a High Performance Health System - Meetings, 2007 July (Box 2, Folder 9-10)
- Commission on a High Performance Health System - Meetings, 2007 November (Box 3, Folder 11)
- Commission on a High Performance Health System - Meetings, 2008 April (Box 3, Folder 12)
- Commission on a High Performance Health System - Meetings, 2008 July (Box 3, Folder 13)
- Commission on a High Performance Health System - Meetings, 2008 November (Box 4, Folder 14-15)
- Commission on a High Performance Health System - Meetings, 2009 April (Box 4, Folder 16)